Benjamin Gerig Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Classified (Box CL 1)
  - Subject file (Box CL 1)
    - State Department (Box CL 1)
      - Colonial policy (Box CL 1)
        - Memoranda and correspondence, 1944-1955, 1961 (Container 4) (Box CL 1)
      - Division of International Security and Organization, Office of Special Political Affairs (Box CL 1)
        - Draft reports regarding the new international organization, 1943-1944 (Container 5) (Box CL 1)
      - Personnel files (Box CL 1)
        - Appointments (Box CL 1)
          - Miscellaneous appointments and travel orders, 1945 (Container 5) (Box CL 1)
      - United Nations (Box CL 1)
        - Trusteeship questions, 1945 (Container 6) (Box CL 1)
      - United Nations Conference on International Organization, San Francisco, Calif. (Box CL 1)
        - Discussions re article five of Trusteeship Chapter, 1945 (Container 6) (Box CL 1)
        - Reports on conference developments, May-June 1945 (Container 6) (Box CL 1)
- Top secret (Box TS 1)
  - Subject file (Box TS 1)
    - Dumbarton Oaks Conference, Washington, D.C. (Box TS 1)
      - Conversations, minutes, and documents, 1944 (Box TS 1)
        - Notebook (Container 2) (Box TS 1)
      - Formulation Group, 1944 (Box TS 1)
        - Memoranda and reports (Container 2) (Box TS 1)
    - United Nations Conference on International Organization, San Francisco, Calif. (Box TS 1)
      - Reports on conference developments, May-June 1945 (Container 6) (Box TS 1)